

CONTACT

- +855-692-65958
- Street 169, Phnom Penh city.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- ReactJS
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS
- · Ant Design
- NestJS

LANGUAGE

Khmer

English

REFERENCES

Khouch Koeun

Deputy Director, Council for the Development of Cambodia

Phone: +855-965-416704

Email: khouch.koeun@cdc.gov.kh

PORFOLIO





SUOS PHEARITH

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT M E

I am a web developer with two years of experience in the industry. I have extensive knowledge of frontend development and APIs related to JavaScript. Through my work as a web developer, I have gained valuable experience and skills.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer | Part Time

CamCyber Ditial Tech Team

· Royal Government of Cambodia Website:

• Design UI

- Build Frontend using NextJS
- · Ministry of Mines and Energy Website:
 - · Build Frontent follow UI using NextJS

Web Developer | Intern

2024 - Present

One Fraternity Co. LTD

- Delivery Route Calculation System | Project Intern:
 - Design UI
 - Design Database follow Requirement
 - Build Frontend and Backend using NextJS and NestJS
- Routing Plan System | Project Bonus:
 - Design UI
 - Design Database
 - Build System using NextJS and NestJS

Web Developer | Freelancer

Independent Freelancer

2022 - 2023

2023 - 2024

- - Requirement Collection
 - Design UI
 - Design Database
 - · Build Frontend using NextJS
 - Build Backend using NestJS

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information and communication Technology

2020 - 2024 Phnom Penh

Institute of Technology of Cambodia

BacII (Certificate of Completion)

2018 - 2020

Prasat Bakong High School

Siem Reap